[Music]
[音乐]
Essen on Saturday evening the police have to
周六晚上吃饭警察必须
mobilize all their reserves in order not to
调动所有储备，以免
fall behind again in
再次落后
the meantime the monopoly on the use of force lay
与此同时，武力的使用受到垄断
with two Arab clans the
即在两个阿拉伯氏族
scene of the spring was a Syrian
叙利亚地区的春天
restaurant in a prime inner-city location on
位于市中心最佳位置的餐厅
Friday evening the restaurant became the
周五晚上餐厅变成了
target of hundreds of men like this
像这样的数百人的目标
tiktok  video shows
抖音视频节目
although the police are on site, dozens of
尽管当地警方正在介入
attackers are penetrating and destroying the
数十名攻击者摧毁了它
furniture
家具
the chaos night in Essen ends in a
埃森的混乱之夜结束于
mass brawl between Syrians and
叙利亚人和叙利亚人之间的大规模争吵
Lebanese
黎巴嫩人
one day after the attack, the
突袭后的一天
restaurant is already well frequented and
当地已经有很多人参加
protected by two police vans
由两辆运兵车保护
Staff
工作人员的要求
but suddenly the boss is supposedly
但老板突然被指控
no longer there or just doesn't want to
不再存在或只是不想存在
talk to us
与我们交谈
we can go again yes the question
我们可以再去 是的问题
is does someone want to say someone wants to
是想表达某人想要某人
say what happened yesterday you the
说昨天发生的事是你死了
pictures are intense so what is why why
图片很暴力所以这是为什么
the trigger for  the orgy of violence is
暴力狂欢的诱因在于
30 kilometers away in Castrop-Rauxel
30 公里外的 Castrop-Rauxel
and the root causes in the Middle East
以及中东更深层次的原因
on Thursday Syrian
周四有叙利亚
refugees in Castrop-Rauxel had
Castrop-Rauxel 成员中的难民
attacked members of a Lebanese clan
遭到黎巴嫩氏族袭击
the family has been living here for 40 years the
这家人在这里住了40年
new neighbors only recently the
最近才有新邻居
result of a tumult
引起骚动
oh
哦
God[ __ ]
上帝 他妈的
[music]
[音乐]
the opponents beat each other up in front of
对手互相殴打
mobile phone cameras and the
运行手机摄像头和
state power can only watch
国家权力只能眼睁睁看着
the police are not as fast as the clans
警察和氏族一样快
we experience an
不是我们在街上遇到过
incredibly fast mobilization on the street when
令人难以置信的快速动员，如果
we intervene as police officers
我们作为女警察进行干预
are police officers at the push of a button several
只需按一下按钮，就有几个警察
10 50 100 people in front  Place and
10 50 100 当地人和
shy police officers police officers and
害羞的警察和警察
third a this quality of mobilization
第三个这个动员质量
only exists in well-stocked structures
只存在于排序良好的结构中
in clan structures that are very
在氏族结构中，它们非常
dangerous and have a special
危险并且有一个特殊的
quality when it comes to violence and threats
暴力和威胁方面的质量
on the street, the
街上也有争吵
Castrop-Rauxel brawl also has a
来自 Castrop-Rauxel 的有一个
history and the  goes like this several
史前史，它是如此之多
Lebanese are said to have beaten a Syrian
据说黎巴嫩人打了一个叙利亚人
and abused his wife
并虐待他的妻子
a
这然后出现在互联网上
statement by a Syrian chief appeared on the internet
叙利亚领导人的声明
the man belongs to a Bedouin tribe
这个人属于贝都因部落
from the east of the country
来自该国东部
the woman was hit on the head
女子头部被击中
I am telling the truth here and I am
我在这里说的是实话
ready for that  to testify everywhere i
准备好见证我说的每一个地方
only say what Allah would agree with
只有安拉会同意的
and Allah says in the Koran attack
安拉在《古兰经》中说
those who attack you as much as they
那些攻击你的人
attacked you
记住他们是如何攻击你的
the Koran the tradition of the Prophet
古兰经 先知的传统
and the customs of our tribe these are
以及我们部落的习俗
our guidelines
我们的政策
and with the moral tailwind off  in
顺风顺水
the desert some Syrians then really turn up the heat on Friday
星期五，沙漠变成了一些叙利亚人
in the city of Essen, the
在埃森市然后真的在上午
most unrest is caused by a hooded man
蒙面人惹的祸最多
who boasts on tiktok there were ten
谁在tiktok上吹嘘有十个
men and we hit them all on the
男人和我们都在
head
撞头
on the other side the
在对面解决
provocations trigger a general mobilization
挑衅总动员
of hundreds of Lebanese  through the
来自数百名黎巴嫩人通过
northern city
北镇
a demonstration of strength in which
实力展示
the Lebanese take power on the streets
黎巴嫩人走上街头掌权
a helpless patrol car
接手一辆无奈的警车
cannot stop the mob as well as
也无法阻止暴民
the conflict is also fueled by a
冲突也来自一个
leader of the Lebanese with
黎巴嫩人的头扇着
a video message to the hooded
给蒙面人的视频信息
Syrian
叙利亚人
two sentences
两句话
either you move  back or we
要么你退休要么我们退休
meet on the battlefield
战场上处处与我们相遇
wherever you want no matter where we are up to the task
无论你想去哪里，无论我们在哪里
be it in Gelsenkirchen in
它生长在盖尔森基兴
Essen or in Dortmund
埃森或多特蒙德
wherever our tribe members
无论我们的部落成员
live
生活
the headquarters of the Lebanese is a
黎巴嫩人的总部是一个
shisha bar in the center of Essen on
埃森市中心的水烟吧
Saturday evening gather here  again
星期六晚上再次聚集在这里
dozens of men
几十个男人
stop insulting someone who is standing in front of
停止侮辱某人之前
our shop
我们的商店
[music]
[音乐]
from here the mob
从这里开始，暴徒在星期五
marched towards the Syrian
向叙利亚进军
restaurant on Friday and nobody
餐厅，但没人吃
stopped him according to Spiegel TV
镜子电视后停止
information, both sides met on
双方已交换信息
Sunday for a peace summit
周日举行和平峰会
whether the conflict  that's the end of it,
知道冲突是否结束
only God knows
可能只有上帝一个人